<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE FreeMedForms>

<DataPack_Pack>

  <PackDescription>
    <!-- Non translatable values -->
    <uuid>freemedforms.certified.icd10.completebase</uuid>
    <authors>Eric Maeker, MD</authors>
    <version>0.7.0</version>
    <fmfv>0.7.0</fmfv>
    <fdv>0.7.0</fdv>
    <cdate>2011-11-26</cdate>
    <lmdate>2012-02-21</lmdate>
    <icon>__theme__/freeicd.png</icon>
    <weblink></weblink>
    <bibliography/>
    <file>icd10/icd10.zip</file>
    <unziptopath>icd10</unziptopath>
    <size>3956</size>
    <md5>a2b08d5dc792be16ddb4a7dec6e85645</md5>
    <sha1></sha1>
    <datatype>ICD</datatype>

    <!-- Translatable values -->
    <license>GPLv3</license>
    <label lang="fr">Classification internationale des maladies</label>
    <label lang="xx">International classification of diseases</label>
    <description lang="fr">Données par défaut pour FreeMedForms (classification internationale des maladies)</description>
    <description lang="xx">Default data for FreeMedForms (international classification of diseases)</description>

    <htmldescription lang="fr">&lt;p>
        La classification internationale des maladies est une classification médicale codifiée
        de maladies et d'une très vaste variété de signes, symptômes, lésions traumatiques,
        empoisonnements, circonstances sociales et causes externes de blessures ou de maladies.
        Elle est publiée par l'Organisation mondiale de la santé (OMS) et est mondialement utilisée
        pour l'enregistrement des causes de morbidité et de mortalité touchant le domaine de la médecine.&lt;br />
        &lt;br />
        FreeMedForms utilise cette classification au sein des antécédents et dans ses moteurs de recherche
        d'interaction médicamenteuses (en particulier le moteur des médicaments potentiellement inappropriés
        en gériatrie).&lt;br />
        &lt;br />
        Son installation est fortement recommandée. Au préalable, il est nécessaire de prendre connaissance
        de la licence de publication et d'en accepter les termes.&lt;br />&lt;/p></htmldescription>

    <htmldescription lang="xx">&lt;p>
        The International Statistical Classification of Diseases and Related Health Problems (most commonly
        known by the abbreviation ICD) is a medical classification that provides codes to classify diseases
        and a wide variety of signs, symptoms, abnormal findings, complaints, social circumstances, and
        external causes of injury or disease. Under this system, every health condition can be assigned to
        a unique category and given a code, up to six characters long. Such categories can include a set of
        similar diseases.&lt;br />
        &lt;br />
        The International Classification of Diseases is published by the World Health Organization (WHO)
        and used worldwide for morbidity and mortality statistics, reimbursement systems, and automated decision
        support in medicine. This system is designed to promote international comparability in the collection,
        processing, classification, and presentation of these statistics. &lt;br />
        &lt;br />
        FreeMedForms uses this classification in the PMHx plugin and in the drug interaction engine (and particularly
        in the potentially inappropriate medications in geriatrics).&lt;br />
        &lt;br />
        Its installation is strongly recommended. But first of all, you must agree the license terms of the ICD10.
        &lt;br />&lt;/p></htmldescription>

    <updateinfo>
      <updateversion from="0.7.0">
        <text lang="fr">Première mise à disposition.</text>
        <text lang="en">First release.</text>
      </updateversion>
    </updateinfo>

  </PackDescription>

</DataPack_Pack>
